Piano music plays
Oh, my God.
Come on, Mom, please buy me a gun.
Well, what do you call
that thing in your hand?
I mean a real one.
You're not old enough, Tawness.
Yes, I am.
I'll clean out the Thomas table every day.
Come on, Mom, please.
I'll be careful, I promise. Please.
Oh, my God!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha...
Ha, ha, ha...
Vasha Stampede, the humanoid
typhoon taken down at Inepril City.
Nice headline.
The 60 billion double dollars is ours!
I'm so excited I can shit.
Not only are we disgustingly rich,
we're going to be famous
across the entire galaxy.
You're acting awfully cautious.
It's okay, he's dead.
I can't help it, it's him lying there.
Hey, cheer up, you look so depressed.
This is a great day for us.
With what we just earned, we can have
this restaurant rebuilt if you want.
Do you mean it?
Damn straight, sweet cheeks.
Me and my esteemed partners
here are multi-billionaires now.
Oh, I'm so relieved.
I was very worried about that.
You reek of tomatoes.
I know.
When I was trying to run away,
it got dumped all over me.
Hey, would you mind reimbursing
me for my dry cleaning?
I'll reimburse you, all right.
With a one-way ticket to the pearly gates!
You're so impatient.
Hey, why do you have to be in such a rush?
Come on, let's just talk it over.
Who the heck are you, mister?
I get so embarrassed when
I have to introduce myself.
But since you were asked,
I'm like a hunter of peace.
One who chases the elusive mayfly of love.
Well, something like that.
Ah, kill that motherfucker!
Are you insane?
Do you want to die stupid?
He just shot us all!
Next time he might use real bullets!
It's okay, shoot if you want.
Try your luck.
No way!
Don't provoke him!
Don't provoke him, Mr.
Potter!
Give it up!
With the exception of this guy, I'm afraid
you've used up all your bullets already.
I don't understand.
How could you tell?
I counted.
Gee, I really hope it's
not cold outside for them.
Here's your gun, partner.
It really helped.
Thank you very much.
That was quite impressive, young man.
A dangerous situation.
Have you always survived like
that without shooting anyone?
Because it's too wasteful.
After all, I can come into
a restaurant like this?
and order an entire stack of pancakes.
for the price of one silly bullet.
You are a strange one.
It seems very odd that you
consider yourself a gunman.
You got a point there.
I'm very sorry.
Huh?
I really hate to do this,
son, but you are Mr.
Vash the Stampede, aren't you?
Uh...
I am sorry.
Please die without the fuss, okay?
I'm sorry about this, Mr. Vash, sir.
Hey. No biggie.
Oh, my gosh.
Half the city is buried in sand.
Their plant probably broke
down and stopped working.
Well, then they should fix it.
Do you have any idea how much repairs
to a plant that size can cost?
Why? Is it expensive?
This time it looks like
the rumors are true.
You're smiling, huh?
I am not smiling.
Now we have to go run risk
prevention and get this documented.
This time we will find the real Vash the
Stampede and bring about his downfall.
Can this be the end?
There he is! In here! Oh crap!
There we go!
That's him!
We've got you now! Oh
really? Do you mean me?
Everyone's so busy today!
Mama, why does this keep happening to me?
I haven't done anything wrong,
but I'm always in trouble and
everybody's always picking on me!
What do I do, Mama?
Oh!
Why am I crying in French?
I see him.
He's up there.
He's all mine!
Get me out of here!
Uh-oh.
Looks like things are getting
pretty heated up down there.
We have to do something before the entire
city and everyone in it is blown away.
But if they're this agitated, I
wonder if it really might be him.
Let's stop this now. Come on.
Hey, wait a minute, Meryl.
Come back.
Meryl!
No!
I like so bad.
I can't stand it!
Damn it!
Who's that deal with
his use of the grenade?
He can't be identified for the reward
if he's a pilot car, you dumbass!
This is bad.
People out of control.
Complete mayhem.
Attention! Excuse me!
If you'll just listen to your mind,
I'm very sorry to disturb you.
My name is Meryl Stryfe from the
Burner Daily Insurance Society,
and I'm here to stay.
The man you're well after,
the one who's known as Bash the
Stampede, is a very dangerous man.
In order to protect your
precious lives and all
of your valuable possessions
from any further home.
This is a message from Mission Control.
Temporarily suspend all
pursuits of Bash the Stampede.
Everybody proceed to base at once.
Ugh, temporarily?
What the hell's the matter with them?
Stop all pursuit now!
Well, what are we supposed
to do now, Chairman?
The damage and casualties are
just getting worse by the moment.
I cannot believe we still haven't caught
this guy after four hours of fighting.
Caught him?
The guy's impossible.
He's managed to run away without
returning a single bullet.
He's just too good for us.
If we make him mad, there's no telling.
Chairman, perhaps we should stop this
while the city is still standing.
That goes without saying.
Where can I find the man in charge?
I need to speak to him.
And just who are you people?
Let me see the man in charge!
How can you allow this to happen?
This is an outrage!
You can't possibly take
out the humanoid typhoon,
no matter how many thousands
of people you set on him.
Uh, yes, I know that
the risk is very high.
But, Miss, you must understand that we
really need that $60 billion double dollars.
It's for the plant, isn't it?
That's right.
Because of a support system bug, over
half of the plant is completely unusable.
But if you mess with Mr.
Vash and the entire city gets wrecked,
you're going to have a lot more
than just the plant to worry about.
Oh, no.
It may already be too late.
I thought we should fight fire with fire,
so that's when I called
in our last resort.
And, sir, just what is our last resort?
Hmm, that. What?
It's over.
It's all over.
Can somebody tell me who or what that is?
It's the Nebraska family.
All right, who's the idiot
that parked this car here?
Are you trying to make
my son trip or what?
Look, you heard him.
Move it now, you damn ignorant drivers.
Let me borrow that thing right now.
Nebraska family, what are you doing here?
Both of you are supposed to be
serving a jail term of 700 years.
Shut your stinking trap.
We released ourselves yesterday
at our own discretion.
That, that is called a jailbreak.
Gee, that's too bad.
And I was getting quite
fond of the quiet life.
But then again,
who can lie idle knowing that 60 billion
double dollars is there for the taking?
Isn't that right, Goofchef?
The infamous Nebraska family.
Convicted felons of over
150 Class A offenses and...
Tell me you're not gonna stick that
big oaf on Vash the Stampede now.
Well, it seemed like a
good idea at the time.
Oh, I'm sick of this!
Why does every situation we run
into take the worst possible turn?
I can't stand it anymore!
We caught Sammy the Stampede! Huh?
Down here, I said we caught
Vash the Stampede! Eh?
Like I said before, we
caught Vash the Stampede!
Do you mean you really caught him?
Well, maybe they've decided
to give up after all, huh?
Ah!
I'm alive!
Oh?
Don't move, Mr. Vash!
Huh? Uh-oh.
Hey, Sandy!
Go tell Control that we've caught him!
We've caught Vash the Stampede!
Tell them to hurry!
Right!
Be quick now!
Bounty hunters in aprons?
Wouldn't want children to see this.
That's right.
We don't want them to see this.
But we have no other choice.
We desperately need money.
I have a son lying sick at home,
but the town doctor decided to take
off and abandon this dying city.
I don't know what's wrong with my boy.
I can't just stand back and wait.
There's no one left to help him here.
That's why, that's why I...
The people, the land, everything went
wrong after the plant malfunctioned.
But not everyone is rich enough
to leave this damned city.
We need money to call the
engineers to fix the plant.
Unless it's repaired,
the city is finished.
Along with everyone in it.
Only one person has to
die to save this city.
So please, Mr.
Vash, give yourself up.
Please don't move.
I understand your situation
better than you know.
However… No! Please, sir! Don't do that!
Until I see this man you're after,
I have no choice but to keep moving!
Now please, for the love of
God, don't shoot that gun.
Everybody get down!
Over there!
Right, I see it!
Bash, the stampede is right over there!
Bingo!
That was so easy!
Almost too easy!
Are you down after only one shot?
That's funny!
That is so funny!
What?
Where was Vash the Stampede?
Huh?
What the hell?
That's him.
The Devil's Helper who single-handedly
reduced a city of one
million people to ashes.
The legendary outlaw Vash the
Stampede is just over that hill.
That can't...
No way!
My, my, that's more like it.
Hey, wait a minute.
Isn't there something
wrong with this picture?
They must know that man can't be him.
Vash the Stampede is a horrible fiend.
If you get in his way,
he can destroy cities.
And he can get out of the
worst situations imaginable.
Even if he's up against a thousand men,
he'd find a way to emerge without a scratch.
That...
that's who...
What now, Vash the Stampede?
That's him, Vash the Stampede.
What's the matter, buddy boy?
Are you chickening out?
Well, aren't you a nice guy?
Hey, time's up, Wonder Boy.
Throw the fear of death
into him, ghost chef.
Chairman, that damn
Nebraska's a loose cannon.
I'm sorry, I didn't
want anyone to get hurt.
How could you do that?
Ugh, I can't believe you both
are still alive and well!
I was kinda hoping you ditch the
woman and save your own skin!
Dash wouldn't do that!
He isn't that kind of person!
Come to think of it...
So you won't kill no matter what, huh?
You are disgusting!
You know what, Vast?
You're nothing but a damn hypocrite!
There's no way you haven't had to kill
troublemakers somewhere along the line!
How do I know?
Because nobody can survive what you've
been through without hurting somebody!
The sixty billion double dollar
bounty on your head is proof of that!
Well, what do you have to say
for yourself, Vasta Stampede?
Why won't he say anything?
Why is he just standing there
taking that kind of abuse?
Hm.
Hm?
You're finally ready to fight, are you?
Oh, so you want to draw.
It's pointless no matter
what caliber pistol you use,
like trying to stop a car from
ramming at 120 miles an hour.
You felt it twice already.
Even your puny brain can realize my son's
fist is a force to be reckoned with,
or do you really believe
you'll survive another one?
This is your last chance to run?
Although no matter how fast you are,
within the next few minutes you'll
be smashed into tiny pieces.
Now pay attention,
because as a courtesy I'm going to lecture
you on just what a stupid
fool you really are.
Using this technique.
My human mincemeat special course.
Go help them, quick.
Enjoy being a hero for a moment,
then die in a most humiliating way.
He did it.
It changed course.
That was great.
He caused my son's fist to be off course
with six little bullets. Not quite, Doc.
I have one left, could be my special one.
My baby!
That was terrible!
I can't believe it!
Did you see what he did?
He really beat him!
And he did it with only six bullets!
Unbelievable!
Suddenly it's become very clear to me
why he is called the Humanoid Typhoon.
It's actually him.
He's for real.
The legendary outlaw.
Bash the Stampede!
You're amazing!
That's nice of you guys to say that,
but I'm no more amazing than you are.
It ain't over yet!
What? What the?
That's twice you've saved me today.
Hey!
Don't ignore me, you!
Don't think you won, even for a second.
Let's call it quits already.
After all now, this land is
made of love and peace! Huh?
Love and peace!
What is he doing?
Come on now, you gotta
write the company reports!
Hurry up!
Love and peace!
M .Stryfe Company report,
four months and 12 days after receiving
our orders for the insurance investigation,
we achieved contact with our
target, the man called Vash.
Contact with our target, the
man simply known as Vash the...
Love and Peace!
No, make it go away!
I can't stand anymore!
Now everybody, join along!
Love and Peace!
Let's go.
I'll see you
next time.
The longer one holds onto a memory,
the longer one lives in the past.
The deeper the memory they hold onto,
the more beautiful the past will become.
The beautiful memories will
eventually turn into hate.
Even if they look ahead, they
lose the ability to walk.
As long as the heavy chain called
revenge continues to bind the heart,
The tears of sadness
will continue to flow.